question_data=[
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Mythology","question":"According to Greek Mythology, Atlas was an Olympian God.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Musicals &amp; Theatres","question":"IMAX stands for Image Maximum.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"The song &quot;Stronger Than You&quot; is a single by Estelle, who played Garnet in Steven Universe.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Lead Singer Rivers Cuomo of American rock band Weezer attended Harvard.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Mythology","question":"According to Greek Mythology, Zeus can control lightning.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Geography","question":"San Marino is the only country completely surrounded by another country.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"History","question":"Adolf Hitler was a german soldier in World War I.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science: Mathematics","question":"An isosceles triangle has two sides of equal length as opposed to three.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}
    ]

# question_data = [
# {"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
# {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "False"},
# {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
# {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
# {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
# {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
# ]